rubratings.com 2017-12-15

# Privacy Policy | The Hottest Site for Body Rubs and Massage Providers

_updated 5/6/2016_

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for (https://rubratings.com). This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:

  1. Where we get our listings.
  2. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
  3. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
  4. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
  5. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

### Where Do We Get Our Listings?

The listings on RubRatings are a combination of user submitted data and listing data acquired through public RSS feeds accessible by anyone with an internet connection. Any data provided on this website including email addresses, names, payment information, phone numbers, or any other personal data is not shared or sold with any other website or party.

The listings are intended to be of consenting adults over the age of 18 that are providing massage services in their area. It is not our wish to display photos or listing data of any person against their will. If you would like your listing removed, please use the ad removal form in the footer of the city listing site.

### User Submitted Information

When you enter information into this website, we may use your information to respond to you regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

Any reviews provided by our users are monitored by admin staff. Personal information, harassing or derogatory language, or any expletive content is removed and not published. The reviews are meant to entertain and inform other users about body rub and massage providers in their area. The reviews are not shared, sold, or sent to any other party including law enforcement or other websites.

### Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contact from us at any time by registered users through our support form on the city listing sites. You can also find out:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

### Security

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Payment information is never saved in our database, and any passwords entered are encyrpted using a strong 256 bit one-way encryption.

### Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

### Cookies

We use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. For instance, when we use a cookie to identify you, you would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

### Updates

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, please contact us through our support form on the city listing sites.

RubRatings Ltd  
71-75 Shelton St Covent Garden  
London, UK WC2H 9JQ
